easyvista.com 2019-01-30

# EasyVista Data & Privacy Policy

EasyVista is a recognized software provider specialized in helping organizations simplify IT Service Management by making it easy to deliver and easy to use for today’s enterprise. EasyVista respects individual privacy of its customers, employees, business partners, visitors and others (Persons Concerned). EasyVista is vigilant to comply with the laws of the countries in which it does business regarding Personal Information that is collected, used, stored, processed and disclosed.

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to:

  * Data collected on EasyVista web-sites for sales and marketing purposes.
  * Data collected for the delivery of the EasyVista software and associated services such as hosting services, consulting, support and training.
  * Data collected for accounting, human resources management and other administrative purposes.

Regarding consent, EasyVista offers Persons Concerned, a choice to opt-out of uses and disclosures of their data that are incompatible with the purposes for which that data was originally collected or subsequently authorized.

When acting as data processor for a customer, EasyVista is not responsible for the obligations of the data controller to obtain from Persons Concerned the appropriate consent to transfer and process their data to EasyVista. As a data processor, EasyVista will not sell, rent, or trade with third parties for their marketing purposes any personal data collected.

In the event that sensitive personal information (pertaining to your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, information related to an individual's health or sexual preference, as well as biometric identifiers, such as finger and voiceprints, and information as to commission or alleged commission of a criminal offense or any related proceedings) to be used for a new purpose or transferred to the control of a third party not acting on behalf of EasyVista, the data subject's explicit consent will be obtained prior to the new use or transfer of the data, unless such new use or transfer is: (1) in the vital interests of the data subject or another person; (2) necessary for the establishment of EasyVista's legal claims of defenses; (3) required to provide medical care or diagnosis; (4) necessary to carry out EasyVista's obligations in the field of employment law; or (5) related to data that are manifestly made public by the data subject. In these cases, data subjects are given notice of such use.

EasyVista takes reasonable and appropriate physical, technical, and organizational measures to protect personal data in its possession from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Even with all these safeguards in place, no method of transmission over the Internet is totally secure and EasyVista does not guarantee the security of personal information transmitted via the Internet.

EasyVista will use personal data only in ways that are compatible with and relevant for the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized. EasyVista takes reasonable and appropriate physical, technical, and organizational measures to ensure that personal data is relevant to its intended use, and that it is accurate, complete, reliable, and current. EasyVista will retain the personal data for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data was collected or for which it is to be further processed.

Data’s subject may contact EasyVista to access their personal data at [privacy@easyvista.com](mailto:privacy@easyvista.com). Upon request, EasyVista will grant reasonable access to personal data. EasyVista will also take reasonable measures to permit data’s subject to access, rectify, erase, restrict processing or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to data’s subject privacy. Furthermore, EasyVista will, upon request of a data’s subject, provide personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.

EasyVista Websites use "cookies". A cookie is a small file that an EasyVista Website may send to your browser. This file is then stored on your hard drive. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to a computer. The cookie saves information regarding your session and account on the EasyVista Website, which the browser passes back to the EasyVista Website's server. Cookies enable EasyVista to build better websites by recording how and when you use the EasyVista Websites and to better serve you when you return to the EasyVista Websites. Cookies are also used to ensure you do not fill out forms on the EasyVista Websites multiple times. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, however, if you disable the cookies, you will not be able to use the EasyVista Websites in the best conditions.

The EasyVista Websites contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) which may be used in some of EasyVista's emails to let EasyVista know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. Some of EasyVista's business partners also employ web beacons that help it better manage content on the EasyVista Websites. However, EasyVista has no access to or control over such web beacons.

The use of cookies by EasyVista's business partners or service providers is not covered by this Policy. EasyVista does not have access or control over those cookies. EasyVista's business partners, and service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the EasyVista Website. Third-party cookies can be disabled via your web browser’s settings.

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if the services are temporarily suspended for maintenance, EasyVista might send you an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications. These communications are not promotional in nature.

EasyVista may amend this Policy from time-to-time, consistent with the requirements of the EU GDPR or EU-US Privacy Shield Principles. When EasyVista does update this Policy, it will also revise the "Last Updated" date at the bottom of this Policy. Any material changes to this Policy will also be posted at https://www.easyvista.com/privacy-policy

**Further information regarding data collection**

Controller: _EasyVista SA  
10 allée Bienvenue  
Immeuble Horizon  
93160 NOISY-LE-GRAND_

 Controller representative: Sylvain GAUTHIER, Chairman & CEO

Legal basis for the processing: Contract and consent

Recipients or categories of recipients: BtoB managers concerned with ITSM software.

Transfer of personal data to a recipient in the United States: EU-US Privacy Shield

Single entry point: [privacy@easyvista.com](mailto:privacy@easyvista.com)

Data storage durations:

  * Contracts duration + 5 years for archiving
  * 10 years for inactive data

The person concerned has the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

**Legal notice related to the edition of the website www.easyvista.com**

The website is edited by EasyVista Inc.   
Incorporation's capital: € 3,145,951.6   
Registration code (R.C.S Bobigny): 347 848 947   
VAT identification number: FR95347848947   
Headquarters: Immeuble Horizon, 10 allée Bienvenue, 93160 NOISY LE GRAND Cedex - FRANCE   
Email: contact@easyvista.com  
Phone: +33 1 55 85 91 00   
Publishing manager: Sylvain GAUTHIER   
Hosted by: HubSpot, Inc., 25 First Street, 2nd Floor, Cambridge, MA 02141 USA, +1 888 482 7768 

Last Updated 

June 26th, 2018
